pastapadre.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | pastapadre.com

“Pastapadre” is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with “Pastapadre” of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.

Therefore, this Privacy Policy Agreement shall apply to “Pastapadre”, and thus shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of [http://www.pastapadre.com](http://www.hitthepass.com/) you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.

### Collection of Information

This website collects various types of information such as:

  * Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies, and server logs.

Rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.

“Pastapadre” may have the occasion to collect anonymous demographic information, such as age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion at a later time. We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior service.

It is highly recommended and suggested that you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a means to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of, and share information collected.

### Use of Information Collected

“Pastapadre” may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of the website.

“Pastapadre” does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent, or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.

“Pastapadre” may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what may be popular to visitors or the general public.

“Pastapadre” may disclose your personal information, without prior notice, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or required in an effort to:

  * Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws, and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon “Pastapadre”.
  * Maintain, safeguard, and/or preserve all rights and/or property of “Pastapadre”
  * Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users

### Children Under Age of 13

“Pastapadre” does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of 13 we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database.

### Unsubscribe or Opt-Out

All users/visitors to “Pastapadre” have the option to discontinue receiving communications from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters.

### Links to Other Websites

“Pastapadre” does contain links to affiliate and other websites. “Pastapadre” does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and solely to the information collected by “Pastapadre”

### Security

“Pastapadre” shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural, and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control.

### Changes to Privacy Policy Agreement

“Pastapadre” reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post any changes that take place so that visitors are always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information.

### Acceptance of Terms

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of the site. In addition, your continued use of “Pastapadre” following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

_If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy feel free to[contact us](http://www.pastapadre.com/contact)._
